[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The meibomian glands are special sebaceous glands located in this part of the human body.", "correct_answer": "Eyelids", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Ear canals", "Lips"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you are in South Central or South Western Pennsylvania and order dippy eggs, what popular way are you ordering your egg to be cooked?", "correct_answer": "Over Easy", "incorrect_answers": ["Omelette", "Poached", "Hard Boiled"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animal is considered a marine mammal because it lives on the sea ice most of the year.", "correct_answer": "Polar bear", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Walrus", "Polar fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tapeti is a nocturnal cottontail rabbit that is indigenous to these areas.", "correct_answer": "Central and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia and Tasmania", "South Asia", "South Africa and Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient of the traditional Swiss dish Rosti?", "correct_answer": "Potatoes", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheese", "Cabbage", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Coca Cola was originally green.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of organism is the Greater Glider, a gliding animal indigenous to Australia?", "correct_answer": "Mammal", "incorrect_answers": ["Reptile", "Fish", "Amphibian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American state produces about 65% of the peaches grown for commercial production in the U.S.A.", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "Colorado", "Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cell nuclei have two primary functions in the cell. The first is to to store genetic information needed for cellular division. What is the second one?", "correct_answer": "To control chemical reactions", "incorrect_answers": ["To maintain an acidic internal pH", "To remove unwanted structural debris surrounding the cell", "To maintain internal hydrostatic pressure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is one day on the planet Neptune?", "correct_answer": "Just over 16 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["Just over 23 hours", "Just under 17 hours", "Just under 10 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What food does Chuck Noland find in one of the boxes from the crashed plane in Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "Chocolates", "incorrect_answers": ["Jelly beans", "Almonds", "Protein supplements"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the most important occupation to Socrates according to Xenophons \u2018Symposium\u2019?", "correct_answer": "Discussing philosophy", "incorrect_answers": ["Creating beauty", "Studying sciences", "Teaching children"]}]